Some of the days that are the hardest are when, you know, I start out first thing in the morning and things just, like I woke up on the wrong side of the bed, or...or whatever, you know, type of phrase you want to use.
But things just don't go right from the very beginning.
You get a late start, you, you know, get to the house and it's an extra big mess, and, you know, you just....one thing after the other just leads to a tough day of...of a long tough day working.
Generally, I...I will schedule two to three houses a day, and if I get a late start then, you know, of course, that just delays the next job, and then the next job, and then it can be seven or eight at night when I get home.
And one thing that I like...I try not to do is to interfere with my client's family time as well. So, when I get a late start, and maybe I have a horrendous house that I had to clean and...and wasn't planning on it, then my day gets later and I start to intrude into their family time.
And...and that makes it tough for me, I don't...I don't like to do that at all. So that's probably the hardest part, is, if I don't start my day right.
So, I kind of have to mentally prepare myself for my day, so, that's probably the hardest day for me, is not preparing myself.
One of my toughest days are Thursdays.
I have lots of clients that want cleaning done Thursdays and Fridays, because they want it done right before the weekend.
So Thursdays are really jam-packed.
I've got three very big jobs, three very big houses that have, you know, three and four bathrooms, and, just large houses...so, that makes for a really long day.
And, I had one of those days where I just woke up and things just didn't want to go my way.
So I...I continued to fight through it, fight through it...didn't feel real great.
So, got in the car, got to the first job, everything went, you know, okay....I was good, but I was still a little bit late.
So, got to the next job, and, you know, moving right along, and I go out to get some cleaning supplies out of my car, and it's locked.
And I go to get my keys out of my little supply box, and they weren't in there, so, I, you know, look around for my keys, and, sure enough, they are locked in my car and I have no extras.
I have none at home, I have no extras, cause I have an extra key in my car, and I have my remote in my car.
And, so, that was kind of tough.
So, I, you know, I had to just fight through the cleaning, and had to have a lock-smith come out and open my doors, and I had to go to another job.
So, you know, sometimes when things just don't go your way...you know, you just have a rough day, and you go to bed that night and you hopefully wake up the next morning and.. and it's all better.